Adam Yonah Trachtman

Full Stack Developer

North District | 052-404-8570 | <u>yonah.trachtman@gmail.com</u> <u>Github | LinkedIn | personal portfolio</u>

SUMMARY

I'm a Full Stack Developer who's been studying coding and have knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, and much more. I have been working on practice projects for my studies. I look forward to learning and improving by getting real-world job experience.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, OOP, SQL, Flask, Django, Javascript, React, Redux, Typescript

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Text Based RPG- Github

A text based RPG game made in python for a hackathon

- Implemented Items and Equipment into the game to add a sense of scaling
- Implemented stats screen in order to be able to check your character's progress
- Troubleshooting and bug testing every time a new feature was implemented

Collaborative Online Whiteboard- Github/Deployed

An online whiteboard made in vite with typescript

- Implemented databases for users and whiteboards
- Implemented The whiteboard functionality
- Troubleshooting and bug testing every time a new feature was implemented

EXPERIENCE

Customer Support Representative

Jerusalem, Israel

TCS Telecom

06/2020 - 06/2021

- Handled calls and emails from customers with speed and efficiency to understand and fix their issue
- Troubleshoot issues for customers in order to help with customer satisfaction and retention
- Served as a stand-in sales rep during summer rush
- Worked with other customer support reps with the same customer based on work scheduled

Armored core Communications Specialist

Many, Israel

IDF

03/2017 - 12/2019

- Preformed daily inspections of equipment to make sure everything was working properly
- Worked with a team for organization and testing of equipment
- Guarded equipment and took inventory on a regular basis

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Ramat Gan, Israel 05/2024 - 09/2024

Frontend Development Hands-on Training Program

Kreativstorm

Remote, Germany 01/2024 - 02/2024

LANGUAGES

English - Native, Hebrew - Intermediate